question_data = [
    {
        "type":"boolean",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "category":"Entertainment: Film",
        "question":"In Alfred Hitchcock's film 'Psycho' it is said he used chocolate syrup to simulate the blood in the famous shower scene.",
        "correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]
    },
    {   "type":"boolean",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "category":"Entertainment: Film",
        "question":"The 2010 film 'The Social Network'; is a biographical drama film about MySpace founder Tom Anderson.",
        "correct_answer":"False",
        "incorrect_answers":["True"]
    },
    {   
        "type":"boolean",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "category":"Entertainment: Film",
        "question":"In the original Star Wars trilogy, Alec Guinness provided the voice for Darth Vader.",
        "correct_answer":"False",
        "incorrect_answers":["True"]
    },
    {
        "type":"boolean",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "category":"Entertainment: Film",
        "question":"The movie 'The Nightmare before Christmas' was all done with physical objects.",
        "correct_answer":"True",
        "incorrect_answers":["False"]
    },
    {
        "type":"boolean",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "category":"Entertainment: Film",
        "question":"'Foodfight!' earned less than $80,000 at box office.",
        "correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]
    },
    {
        "type":"boolean",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "category":"Entertainment: Film",
        "question":"The film '2001: A Space Odyssey' was released on December 31st, 2000.",
        "correct_answer":"False",
        "incorrect_answers":["True"]
    },
    {
        "type":"boolean",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "category":"Entertainment: Film",
        "question":"Ewan McGregor did not know the name of the second prequel film of Star Wars during and after filming.",
        "correct_answer":"True",
        "incorrect_answers":["False"]
    },
    {
        "type":"boolean",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "category":"Entertainment: Film",
        "question":"Han Solo's co-pilot and best friend, 'Chewbacca', is an Ewok.",
        "correct_answer":"False",
        "incorrect_answers":["True"]
    },
    {
        "type":"boolean",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "category":"Entertainment: Film",
        "question":"The word 'Inception' came from the 2010 blockbuster hit 'Inception'.",
        "correct_answer":"False",
        "incorrect_answers":["True"]
    },
    {
        "type":"boolean",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "category":"Entertainment: Film",
        "question":"Actor Tommy Chong served prison time.",
        "correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]
    }
]
